Guide to the Stephen Sandy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Stephen Sandy papers
1925-2012
YCAL MSS 744
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
35.36
(54 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
The Stephen Sandy Papers consist of correspondence, subject files, writings, personal papers, printed material, photographs, and audiovisual material created and accumulated by American poet Stephen Sandy. The papers document the creation, publication, and reception of Sandy's work from his earliest pamphlet, Mary Baldwin (1962), to more recent work, shedding light on Sandy's poetic sensibility and his personal and professional relationships with other poets. Significant quantities of material relate to his work at Bennington College.
Sandy, Stephen
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired by gift and purchase, on various funds, from Stephen Sandy (Yale 1955), 2001-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 29-30, 45 (audio and video recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 49, 50 (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Stephen Sandy (1934-)
Stephen Sandy is an American poet. Born in 1934, he received a B.A. in English from Yale in 1955 and a Ph.D. in English from Harvard in 1963. He has taught at Boston University, Brown University, and Bennington College. His works include: Netsuke Days (2008), Weathers Permitting (2005), Surface Impressions: A Poem in Eight Parts (2002), Black Box (1999), and The Thread: New and Selected Poems (1998). Sandy is the poet featured in the documentary The Biologist, the Poet and the Funeral Director (2007), directed by Harvey Edwards.
More information about Stephen Sandy can be found on his web site.
Scope and Contents
The Stephen Sandy Papers consist of correspondence, subject files, writings, personal papers, printed material, photographs, and audiovisual material created and accumulated by American poet Stephen Sandy. The papers document the creation, publication, and reception of Sandy's work from his earliest pamphlet, Mary Baldwin (1962), to more recent work, shedding light on Sandy's poetic sensibility and his personal and professional relationships with other poets. Significant quantities of material relate to his work at Bennington College.
Arrangement
Organized into sixteen groupings: I. January 2001 Acquisition. II. February 2002 Acquisition. III. May 2002 Acquisition. IV. July 2003 Acquisition. V. February 2006 Acquisition. VI. April 2006 Acquisition. VII. July 2006 Acquisition. VIII. August 2006 Acquisition. IX. October 2006 Acquisition. X. May 2008 Acquisition. XI. June 2008 Acquisition. XII. June 2009 Acquisition. XIII. June 2011 Acquisition. XIV. December 2011 Acquisition. XV. February 2012 Acquisition. XVI. July 2012 Acquisition.
Material within this collection has been organized by acquisition reflecting the fact that the collection has been acquired in increments over time.
Researchers should note that material within each acquisition overlaps with and/or relates to material found in other acquisitions. In order to locate all relevant material within this collection, researchers will need to consult each acquisition described in the Collection Contents section. Material can be arranged differently in each acquisition, depending on how the material was organized when it was received by the library.
American literature -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Diaries; Photographs; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Poets -- United States -- 20th Century; Sandy, Stephen; Bennington College -- Faculty
- January 2001 Acquisition, 1977-1994; 1; 0.21; (1 box)
  Scope and Contents
  The January 2001 Acquisition consists of material removed from books acquired from Stephen Sandy. Material consists of correspondence, notes, and writings of Stephen Sandy, including the poem "Hogback Lookout," draft, typescript, annotated.
  Arrangement
  Organized under two headings: Correspondence and Notes, and Writings.
  - Correspondence and Notes
    - Bennington College, President's Office, 1994 January 11 (Box 1)
    - David, 1990 January 19 (Box 1)
    - Gibson, Gail McMurray, undated (Box 1)
    - JR, undated (Box 1)
    - Knight, Etheridge, undated (Box 1)
    - McRay, Paul, undated (Box 1)
    - Sandy, Stephen, undated; 3 (Box 1)
    - Trawick, Leonard, 1985 February 6 (Box 1)
    - Wellman, John, 1977 April 12 (Box 1)
  - Writings
    - "Hogback Lookout", undated (Box 1)
    - "In a short span of years, Sven Birkerts...", undated (Box 1)
- February 2002 Acquisition, 1985-1993; 2; 0.21; (1 box)
  The February 2002 Acquisition consists of material removed from books acquired from Stephen Sandy, including correspondence, newspaper clippings, and notes.
  - Typed letter signed from Sandy to Galway Kinnell, undated (Box 2)
  - Typed letter from Greg Paper to Sandy, 1993 February 14 (Box 2)
  - Newspaper clipping and notes, 1985 (Box 2)
- May 2002 Acquisition, 1968; 3; 0.21; (1 box)
  The May 2002 Acquisition consists of an autograph album, and of material removed from books acquired from Stephen Sandy.
  - Autograph album presented to Stephen Sandy upon his departure from Tokyo, 1968 July 19 (Box 3)
  - Material removed from Stephen Sandy's books, 2 (Box 3)
- July 2003 Acquisition, 1938-2003; 4; 15.83; (17 boxes)
  Organized under three headings: Correspondence and Subject Files, Writings, and Other Papers.
  The July 2003 Acquisition consists of correspondence, writings, printed material, and other papers. The Correspondence and Subject Files consist chiefly of professional and personal letters from writers, documenting the literary community in which Sandy is active, and related papers. Other subject files consist of material relating to a particular person or topic (e.g. W. H. Auden). Writings include drafts (autograph manuscript and typescript), proofs, and printed versions, some corrected.
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Aaron, Jonathan, 1971 July 9 (Box 4)
    - Abbott, Anthony, undated (Box 4)
    - Academy of American Poets, 1998, undated (Box 4)
    - Adams, Hunter, 1994 June 8 (Box 4)
    - Alfred, William, 1971-1981 (Box 4)
    - Allen, Jennifer, 1990 0ctober 22 (Box 4)
    - Allen, Paul, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Allman, John, 1964 June 2 (Box 4)
    - Ames, Elizabeth, 1964-1975, undated (Box 4)
    - Ammons, A. R., 1971-1999 (Box 4)
    - Anders, Shirley, 1985-1989 (Box 4)
    - Andrews, Mary Ellen, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
    - The Antioch Press, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Applewhite, James, 1983-1994 (Box 4)
    - Arvio, Sarah, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
    - Ascher, Barbara Lazear, 1994-1995; 2 (Box 4)
    - Asekoff, Lou S., 1988-2001 (Box 4)
    - Ashbery, John, 1978-1996 (Box 4)
    - Ashworth, Andrea, 1997-2000 (Box 4)
    - The Atlantic Monthly, 1966-2000 (Box 4)
    - Auden, W. H., 1939-2000, undated; 3 (Box 4)
    - Bach, Steven, 2002, undated (Box 4)
    - Balakian, Peter, 1982, undated (Box 4)
    - Bangs, Carol, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Barks, Coleman, 2000 February 7 (Box 4)
    - Barlow, Harriet, 1991-1993, undated (Box 4)
    - Barr, John, 1968-2003, undated; 2 (Box 4)
    - Barrow Street, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Barzun, Jacques, 1938-1939 (Box 4)
    - Bate, Walter Jackson, 1983-1987 (Box 4)
    - Bauer, Douglas, 1995-1996, undated (Box 4)
    - Beale, Arthur, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Belitt, Ben, 1973-1996, undated (Box 4)
    - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1998-2000 (Box 4)
    - Belton, Don, 1988-1996 (Box 4)
    - Bennington College, 1972-2000, undated (Box 4)
    - Bentley, Eric, undated (Box 4)
    - Bercovitch, Sacvan, 1988 April 14 (Box 4)
    - Bernard, April, 2000-2002 (Box 4)
    - Bernold, André, 1992-1996 (Box 4)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1982 August 18 (Box 4)
    - Bertolino, James, 1973 October 19 (Box 4)
    - Bidart, Frank, 1993-2000, undated (Box 4)
    - Birkerts, Sven, 1987-1996 (Box 4)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Black, Sophie Cabot, 1996 August 8 (Box 4)
    - Black, Star, 2001-2002, undated (Box 4)
    - Blaise, Clark, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Blake, Schooz, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Bloch, Chana, 1997-1999, undated (Box 4)
    - Bloom, Harold, undated (Box 4)
    - Bloom, Jim, 1983-1990 (Box 4)
    - Blum, Etta, 1966-1969, undated (Box 4)
    - Blumenthal, Michael, 1991 August 17 (Box 4)
    - Bly, Robert, 1959, undated (Box 4)
    - Böhlke, Rainer, 1996 August 21 (Box 4)
    - Boepple, Willard, 1985-2001 (Box 4)
    - Bond, William, 1986 March 7 (Box 5)
    - Borestone Mountain Poetry Awards, 1962 May 8 (Box 5)
    - Boulevard, 1985-1998 (Box 5)
    - Bourgeau Family, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - Boyers, Robert, 1986-1995 (Box 5)
    - Brant, Henry, undated (Box 5)
    - Bread Loaf Writers' Conference, 1967 April 11 (Box 5)
    - Brewer, Helene, 1971 October 7 (Box 5)
    - Bristow, Amanda, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Brock-Broide, Lucie, 1990-1995 (Box 5)
    - Bromige, David, 1993 January 2 (Box 5)
    - Brooke, Nicholas and Julie, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
    - Brookhouse, Christopher, 1996-1998, undated (Box 5)
    - Brooks, Cleanth, [no year] August 10 (Box 5)
    - Brown University & Bennington, 1969-1984, undated (Box 5)
    - Browne, Michael Dennis, 1975, undated (Box 5)
    - Browne, Robert Blaine, 1953-1969 (Box 5)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew, 1988 April 19 (Box 5)
    - Bruchac, Joseph, undated (Box 5)
    - Brynteson, Susan, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Bubriski, Kevin, 1996 July 26 (Box 5)
    - Buckley, Jerome Hamilton, 1967-1986 (Box 5)
    - Buechner, Katherine, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Burke, Steven, undated (Box 5)
    - Burkhardt, Frederick, 1995-1999 (Box 5)
    - Burris, Sidney, 1982 September 5 (Box 5)
    - Busch, Frederick, 1975, undated (Box 5)
    - Butts, Bill, 1988 August 3 (Box 5)
    - Byrom, Thomas (Bill), 1972, undated (Box 5)
    - Caldwell, Joseph, 1987-1998 (Box 5)
    - Calleo, David P., 1973-1998 (Box 5)
    - Cambridge Center for Adult Education, 1963 February 19 (Box 5)
    - Carruth, Hayden, 1975-1987 (Box 5)
    - Carson, Josephine (Ryder), 1976-2001, undated (Box 5)
    - Casey, Michael, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
    - Cassill, R. V., 1976 September 2 (Box 5)
    - Chao, Phebe, 1983-2001 (Box 5)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1983-1996, undated (Box 5)
    - Chasin, Helen, 1978 July (Box 5)
    - Cheever, John, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Cherry, Kelly, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1991-1998 (Box 5)
    - The Chicago Review, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - Clampitt, Amy, 1983-1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Clausen, Wendell, 1991-1993 (Box 5)
    - Cole, Henri, 1993, undated (Box 5)
    - Coleman, Elizabeth, 1994-2000; 2 (Box 5)
    - Contemporary Authors, Dictionary of Literary Biography, 1994-1995, undated (Box 5)
    - Corbett, William, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Cordova, José, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Corkery, Christopher Jane, 1991-1996 (Box 5)
    - Corman, Cid, 1966-1992, undated (Box 5)
    - Corn, Alfred, 1994-1997 (Box 5)
    - Corriveau, Art, 2000 December 1 (Box 5)
    - Costanzo, Gerald, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Costin, Canon Kenneth, 1994 July 14 (Box 5)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1966-1985 (Box 5)
    - Cox, Elizabeth (Betsy), 1996 September (Box 5)
    - Cramer, Steven, 1987-2000, undated (Box 5)
    - Crane, Hart, 1939 (Box 5)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1973-1999 (Box 5)
    - Crews, Frederick, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Cross, Louise, 1995 January 19 (Box 5)
    - Culver, John, 1971 September 23 (Box 5)
    - Cumming, Douglas, 1975-2002 (Box 5)
    - Currier, Douglas, 1995-1999 (Box 5)
    - Curtis, John and Susan, 1974-2001 (Box 5)
    - Daniel, David, 1998-2002 (Box 6)
    - Davidson College, 1988-1994, undated (Box 6)
    - Davis, Kathryn and Eric Zencey, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Davis, Stuart, 1968 January 2 (Box 6)
    - Davison, Peter, 1978-2002, undated; 2 (Box 6)
    - Delbanco, Nicholas, 1966-2001; 2 (Box 6)
    - De Los Reyes, August, 1994-1996 (Box 6)
    - DeNiord, Chard, 1980-2002, undated; 2 (Box 6)
    - Dennis, Carl, 1991-2002 (Box 6)
    - Derhovanessian, Diana, [no year] November 6 (Box 6)
    - Desai, Kiran, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Dibbell, David, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Dickey, James, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Diggory, Terence, 1986-1988 (Box 6)
    - Dobyns, Stephen, 1975 January 28 (Box 6)
    - Dodd, Susan, 1994-1996 (Box 6)
    - Donaldson, Scott, 1983-1998 (Box 6)
    - Dorfman, Elsa, 1975-1998, undated (Box 6)
    - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1963-1964; 2 (Box 6)
    - Dove, Rita, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Dubie, Norman, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Dunn, Stephen, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - Easterly, John, 1997-1999, undated (Box 6)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1987 October 17 (Box 6)
    - Edmundson, Mark, 1976-1995; 2 (Box 6)
    - Eide, Elling O., 1968-1973 (Box 6)
    - Elbers, Johan, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Ellmann, Richard (Dick), 1984 July 23 (Box 6)
    - Elman, Richard, 1983, undated (Box 6)
    - Emanuel, Lynn, 1983-1996 (Box 6)
    - Empty Elevator Shaft Press, 1974, undated (Box 6)
    - Endo, Russell, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Engel, Monroe, [no year] January 20 (Box 6)
    - Engels, John, 1973-1978 (Box 6)
    - Enslin, Theodore, 1980 October 17 (Box 6)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1976-1981 (Box 6)
    - Feinman, Alvin, undated (Box 6)
    - Felstiner, John, 1998-2001 (Box 6)
    - Ferguson, William, 1965 October 27 (Box 6)
    - Fine, Vivian, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Finley, Tom, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert, 1979 January 28 (Box 6)
    - Forbes, Crosby, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Ford, Harry, 1988-1999 (Box 6)
    - Foster, Kit, undated (Box 6)
    - Foster, Tom, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
    - Frank, Elizabeth, [1995] (Box 6)
    - Franklin, Cornell, 1971, undated (Box 7)
    - Franzen, Jonathan, 1992-1994 (Box 7)
    - Freas, Donald, 1997, undated (Box 7)
    - Frede, Richard, 1974-1999 (Box 7)
    - Fredericks, Claude and David Beeken, 1972-1988, undated (Box 7)
    - Freed, Lynn, 1987-1997, undated (Box 7)
    - Freeman, Arthur, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
    - Friedlander, Beau, 1993-1998 (Box 7)
    - Friedlander, Marc, 1962 March 30 (Box 7)
    - Friedman, Alan, 1973 December 17 (Box 7)
    - Frost, Robert, undated (Box 7)
    - Fruchtbaum, Harold, 1970 November 22 (Box 7)
    - Frumkes, Lewis Burke, 1992-1994, undated (Box 7)
    - Frym, Gloria, 1996-1999, undated (Box 7)
    - Fulton, Alice, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
    - Furman, Laura, 1973 July 15 (Box 7)
    - Galassi, Jonathan, 1974-1981 (Box 7)
    - Gale Research, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
    - Galvin, Brendan, [no year] September (Box 7)
    - Gardner, Isabella, 1966-1991 (Box 7)
    - Garrett, George, 1979-2001, undated (Box 7)
    - Gass, William, 1969-1995, undated (Box 7)
    - Geldzahler, Henry, 1983, undated (Box 7)
    - Giannini, David, 1982 October 14 (Box 7)
    - Gibbon, Reginald, 1981 May 14 (Box 7)
    - Gibson, Gail, 1994, undated (Box 7)
    - Gifford, Don, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Gioia, Dana, 1992-1996 (Box 7)
    - Gittings, Robert, 1966 November 25 (Box 7)
    - Glazier, Lyle, 1982 September 8 (Box 7)
    - Glück, Louise, circa 1978 (Box 7)
    - Godwin, Rebecca, 1998-2001 (Box 7)
    - Goldensohn, Barry and Lorrie, 1983, undated (Box 7)
    - Goldstein, Frederick, 1993 May 21 (Box 7)
    - Goldstein, Laurence, 1981-2000 (Box 7)
    - Grealy, Lucie, 2000-2002 (Box 7)
    - Greene, Nicky, undated (Box 7)
    - Greenhouse, Stuart, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Grenier, Robert, 1980 October 23 (Box 7)
    - Grolier Bookshop, 1998-2002 (Box 7)
    - Gross, Matthew, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Gross, Tina, 1985-1996 (Box 7)
    - Grossman, Allan and Judith, 1998, undated (Box 7)
    - Gulick, Robert S., 2000-2002 (Box 7)
    - Gurganus, Allan, 1976-1995 (Box 7)
    - Guy, Georges, 1973-1997, undated (Box 7)
    - H., Priscilla (Bennington College), 2002 March 28 (Box 7)
    - Hadas, Rachel, 1982-2002, undated; 2 (Box 7)
    - Hagen, Daron, 1997-1999 (Box 7)
    - Hall, Donald, 1978-2002, undated (Box 7)
    - Hall-Heckscher, Lavinia, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Hanks, Jane, 1983-1996 (Box 7)
    - Hanson, Pauline, [no year] October 11 (Box 7)
    - Harper's Monthly Magazine, 1962 June 29 (Box 7)
    - Harper, Michael, 1981 August 24 (Box 7)
    - Harris, Dale, undated (Box 7)
    - Harrison, Jeffrey, 1991-1996 (Box 7)
    - Hart, Henry, 1995-1999, undated (Box 7)
    - Hartlage, Ben F., 1996-1998, undated (Box 7)
    - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1970 August 31 (Box 7)
    - Harvard Review, 1998-2001, undated (Box 7)
    - Harvard University. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1961 May 10 (Box 7)
    - Harvard University. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1962 May 2 (Box 7)
    - Havlik, Dan, 1991 October 28 (Box 7)
    - Heaney, Seamus, 1992-1994 (Box 7)
    - Hearst, James, 1982 August 15 (Box 7)
    - Hecht, Anthony, 1979 November 22 (Box 7)
    - Hedin, Robert, 1983 November 28 (Box 7)
    - Heffner, Ray, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Held, Julius, 1991-2000, undated (Box 7)
    - Hempel, Amy, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Hersey, John, 1966 August 5 (Box 8)
    - Hiatt, Suzanne, 1986-1998, undated (Box 8)
    - Hilles, Frederick W., 1955 June 6 (Box 8)
    - Hine, Daryl, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - Hirsch, Edward, 1987 July 1 (Box 8)
    - Hirshfield, Jane, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - Hitchcock, George, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
    - Hoagland, Edward, 1992-2002, undated (Box 8)
    - Hoffman, Jill, 1981-2002 (Box 8)
    - Holland, Gill, 1998, undated (Box 8)
    - Hollander, John, 1991-1993 (Box 8)
    - Holmes, Ted, 1960-1965, undated (Box 8)
    - Honig, Edwin, 1967-1994 (Box 8)
    - Hood Museum, 1998, undated (Box 8)
    - Hooker, Michael, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Horowitz, Evelyn, 1967-2002, undated (Box 8)
    - Horsting, Eric, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, circa 1925-2002; 18 (Box 8)
    - Howard, Richard, 1967-2001, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Howe, Fanny Quincy, 1967-1987 (Box 8)
    - Howes, Barbara, 1970-1990 (Box 8)
    - Hoyem, Andrew, 1973 September 8 (Box 8)
    - Huang, C. C., 1995-2000, undated (Box 8)
    - Hubbard, Sue, 1997-1998, undated (Box 8)
    - Huynh, Jade, 1988-1993, undated (Box 8)
    - Hyman, Stanley, 1970 June 18 (Box 8)
    - Inez, Colette, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Ingolsfrud, Cathryn, 1996 September 15 (Box 8)
    - Irby, Kenneth, 1970-1983, undated (Box 8)
    - James, Henry, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Janeway, Michael, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
    - The Johns Hopkins University Press, 1991-1994 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Buffie, [no year] August 31 (Box 8)
    - Kafka, Kimberley, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Kennedy, Frederick, 1994 December 13 (Box 8)
    - Kennedy, Hugh, 1993-1996 (Box 8)
    - Kennedy, X. J., 1971-1991, undated (Box 8)
    - Kenney, Richard, 1976-1987, undated (Box 8)
    - The Kenyon Review, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
    - Kessler, Milton, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1990 October 1 (Box 8)
    - Kinzie, Mary, 1994 August (Box 8)
    - Kirchwey, Karl, 1988-2001 (Box 8)
    - Kiteley, Brian, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - Klappert, Peter, 1988 May 2 (Box 8)
    - Klein, Michael, 1987-1993 (Box 8)
    - Klinkenborg, Verlyn, 1995 January 30 (Box 8)
    - Knopf, Alfred, 1964-1992 (Box 8)
      General note
      File relates to the publication of Thanksgiving Over Water.
    - Knox, Bernard, undated (Box 8)
    - Koch, Kenneth, 1980, undated (Box 8)
    - Kortick, Roy, 1997 December 10 (Box 8)
    - Kumin, Maxine, 1980-1998 (Box 8)
    - Kuusisto, Stephen, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Kuzma, Greg, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Lane, John, 1994-2002; 2 (Box 9)
    - Lansing, Gerrit, 2000 July 31 (Box 9)
    - Lanyon, Ellen, 1998-2001 (Box 9)
    - Lanza, Frances, 1987 December 28 (Box 9)
    - Lasalle, Peter, 1977-1987 (Box 9)
    - Lathbury, Roger, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Latuchie, Karen, 1984-2002, undated; 2 (Box 9)
    - Lea, Sydney, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Leary, Paris, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Lehman, David, 1981-1997, undated (Box 9)
    - Lehman, Eric, 1998-2000 (Box 9)
    - Leib, Jeffrey, 1993-1995 (Box 9)
    - Leibowitz, Herbert, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
    - Lein, David, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
    - Lemann, Charlotte, 1995, undated (Box 9)
    - Lethem, Jonathan, 2000-2001 (Box 9)
    - Levin, Phillis, 1992-1997 (Box 9)
    - Levine, Jeffrey, undated (Box 9)
    - Levis, Larry, 1982 September 24 (Box 9)
    - Lieberman, Laurence, 1979 September 27 (Box 9)
    - Lifson, Martha Ronk, undated (Box 9)
    - Linney, Romulus, undated (Box 9)
    - Liu, Timothy, 1999-2001 (Box 9)
    - Livings, Jack, 1996-1998 (Box 9)
    - Locklair, Dan, 1986-1994 (Box 9)
    - Lombardy, Anthony, 1994 June 30 (Box 9)
    - Lord Gowrie, 2001 July 31 (Box 9)
    - Lott, Bret, 1988 November 14 (Box 9)
    - Louisiana State University Press, 1997-1999 (Box 9)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1963-1998 (Box 9)
    - Ludvigson, Susan, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - Luening, Otto, undated (Box 9)
    - Lum, Wing Tek, 1972-1994, undated (Box 9)
    - Lytle, Andrew, 1966 April 5 (Box 9)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1964-1978, undated (Box 9)
    - Macbeth, George, undated (Box 9)
    - Maekawa, Yuichi, 1982 March 25 (Box 9)
    - Magowan, Robin, 1995-2001 (Box 9)
    - Maguire, Gregory, 1988-2001 (Box 9)
    - Mailer, Norman, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Malaguti, Andrea, undated (Box 9)
    - Malamud, Bernard and Ann, 1976-1997, undated (Box 9)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1976-1998; 2 (Box 9)
    - Marchant, Fred, 1993-1995, undated (Box 9)
    - Maris, Kathryn, 1998-2000 (Box 9)
    - Markowitz, Mitch, 1977-1998 (Box 9)
    - Martin, Harold C., 1988-1996 (Box 9)
    - Martin, Linda Wagner (Plath), 1985-1990 (Box 9)
    - Maso, Carole, 1995 July 25 (Box 9)
    - Mason, Jerry, 2000-2002 (Box 9)
    - The Massachusetts Review, 1960 October 5 (Box 9)
    - Mathews, Harry, 1979-2001, undated (Box 9)
    - Matthews, William, 1977-1997, undated (Box 9)
    - Mattison, Alice, 1996 July 22 (Box 9)
    - Mayhall, Jane, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - Mazur, Gail, 1995 (Box 9)
    - McCarthy, Eugene J., 1967 May 20 (Box 9)
    - McClatchy, J. D., 1986-2001, undated (Box 9)
    - McCullough, David, 1995-2001 (Box 9)
    - McFall, Gardner, 1987-2001 (Box 9)
    - McHugh, Heather, 1977-1984 (Box 10)
    - McManus, Kevin, 1987-1994 (Box 10)
    - McRay, Paul, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Meiji University, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Melnyczuk, Askold, 1995-1996 (Box 10)
    - Mendelson, Edward, 1992-1997 (Box 10)
    - Meredith, William, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Merrill, James, 1977-2001, undated; 3 (Box 10)
    - Merullo, Roland, 1997-2000 (Box 10)
    - Merwin, W. S. (William Stanley), 1971-2001 (Box 10)
    - Merz, Terri, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Miles, Josephine, 1961 October 16 (Box 10)
    - Miller, Chris, [2002] (Box 10)
    - Miller, Ethelbert, 1988 April 18 (Box 10)
    - Miller, Heather Ross, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Miller, Marcus, 1992, undated (Box 10)
    - Miller, Sue, 1987, undated (Box 10)
    - The Minnesota Review, 1960-1962, undated (Box 10)
    - Mirsky, Mark, 1971 October 10 (Box 10)
    - Mitchell, Roger, 1989 November 1 (Box 10)
    - Mitten, David, 1986-2002 (Box 10)
    - Mondale, Walter F., 1967 April 12 (Box 10)
    - Morgan, Elizabeth, 1987-1998; 2 (Box 10)
    - Morgan, Frederick, 1972-1978 (Box 10)
    - Morgan, Robert, 1994 May 4 (Box 10)
    - Morris, Wright, undated (Box 10)
    - Morrison, Micah, 1992-2002 (Box 10)
    - Morvins, Geoffrey, 1970 September 4 (Box 10)
    - Moss, Howard, 1968-1987 (Box 10)
    - Movius, Geoffrey and Barbara, 1967-2001, undated (Box 10)
    - Muldoon, Paul, 1999 December 28 (Box 10)
    - Muratori, Fred, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Murray, Joan, undated (Box 10)
    - Murray, Nancy, 1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Navasky, Bruno, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Nemerov, Howard, [no year] October 1 (Box 10)
    - New York Times, 1970 (Box 10)
    - The New Yorker, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
    - Nims, John Frederick, 1964-1993 (Box 10)
    - Noland, Kenneth and Peggy, 1983-1998, undated (Box 10)
    - Noonan, John F., 1978 (Box 10)
    - Norris, Kathleen, 1994-1995 (Box 10)